Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
Hello.
I'm Sakurazuki46.
Today I have a card game for you.
When I first started youtube, there was a game available on the site.
I was excited to play.
Do you remember when I was so excited to play it?
Well, we couldn't do it because it was time for the live stream.
So they said we'll do it another time.
I thought it was just going to go away, but...
But then they said they'd let me do it today.
They remembered me.
I really felt the love.
Punch time!
Hey, Punch Time!
Punch!
Punch, right?
Punch?
Punch!
Helping parents.
Yay!
Speak!
We've also gathered five people who are willing to play with us in a friendly manner.
Ito-chan is the representative of the smiling group.
She enjoys doing everything.
I'm really excited to be here today!
And Ten-san is the youngest of the second term students.
I was wondering if you think I'm still a bit childish.
So he's going to introduce them to us.
And these two in the middle have baby-like faces.
The art of putting it all together.
Okay, let's play a game I really love, I love, I love, I love...
I love it, and we just played it recently.
Don't tell me.
I did.
I'll save you the time of explaining the rules, and while I'm at it, I'll do a little magic.
You want to do it?
You're gonna do it?
Can I ask you to say "stop"?
Yes, please.
Stop.
Yes, sir.
And may I ask you to look at this top card?
Yes, please.
Let's see it for the camera.
Here it is.
Okay.
Can I borrow this for a second?
Can I borrow it for a second?
Yes, sir.
Can I put it in here?
But there's a lot of stuff here.
I'll give you a lot.
Wow, I don't get it.
It's like an ace.
Okay, okay.
You're talking about this, aren't you?
What?
That's amazing.
You want to do it again?
It's okay.
What? Do you have any rubber bands, or do I even have rubber bands?
Okay, okay, okay.
I've failed at that before.
All right, let's do this.
Clockwise?
Let's go clockwise.
Clockwise.
When you take this out, turn it this way so I don't see it.
Oh!
That's the style.
That's good.
Okay, let's go.
Okay.
Here you go.
LaLaLaLaLaLaLaLaLaLaLaLaLa
Panch perm. Well, sure.
Oh, melon-boze. Melon-boze.
Hardly.
Soramame
They're so cute.
So far, they're all green.
How do you get them out?
Like this.
That's right.
Excuse me.
SpongeBob.
I was thinking the same thing.
No kidding?
I'm not lying.
Not even one of these.
There are so many kinds.
Offtan.
They'll be here soon.
It's about time.
What's that called?
What's that?
When you get a nosebleed, you hold it here to stop the bleeding.
Yes, that's right.
Stop nosebleed.
Stop nosebleed
Stop the nosebleed.
There's a chance it's coming.
I don't know.
Who's this?
Nice to meet you.
Okay, bye.
Banana bangs.
Who is it?
Isn't that a lot of water?
It's a lot of water.
Mittens.
Mittens?
What are mittens?
Grab a handful.
I see.
You know what they are.
And...
Crackle, crackle, crackle.
He called me.
Who's that?
Who?
Rock, paper, scissors.
That's a big one.
Is it all there?
Punch, punch, punch, punch.
Oh, no.
You're not very good at the first one.
Punch and punch... be careful.
Punch and punch.
Be careful.
Yes, sir.
What's this?
Sacajawea Bonds.
I'm kind of on the edge myself.
Nazcan.
Ready, go!
I see it, I see it, I see it.
Yay!
Airey.
I only remember Nazcan.
I think I'm going to be too loud.
Emishi Banana
Paper banana
Maybe it was with the tension.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors
Rock, paper, scissors!
It's aiko!
Noisy!
I can't hear the vibrato!
I can't hear the vibrato.
Here we go!
Punch Perlman!
Who's Punch Perlman?
Who's Punch-Perman?
Punch Paperman!
Maybe Airi was a little quicker.
Punch Perman is almost
I'm so embarrassed.
I see it, I see it.
What's wrong with his voice?
Here we go.
Punch it, permerman!
Panch perm!
Punch permanent wave
Oh, really?
You're making good money.
That's funny.
Who's this?
Nice to meet you.
How do you do?
I have a straight perm.
No way!
Don't do that.
Straight perm.
Oh!
What's this?
Okay, then.
She's cute.
I'll call her Kira.
Kira? That's nice.
It's easy to understand.
Good morning!
But I didn't remember.
I thought you were a sponge.
Two and a half degrees in two and a half.
Wow!
That's a big one.
Punch it!
Punch pan!
Hey, Punch Punch Punch!
Oh, man.
Punch Pants collection.
Oh, no!
Melon Bozu!
Melon Boze collection started
Punch bread!
Sora why!
Sora-why!
10,000 yen.
Getz, you're out.
There you go!
Here we go.
He's so cute.
Okay, okay, okay!
Oh, yeah!
You squeezed it.
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK!
Okay, okay, okay.
Here we go.
First time?
First time.
It's like heaven.
Why don't you call it "heavenly"?
Let's go with "heavenly"?
Tensama.
Ten-sama.
Let's go!
Ready?
Kira-chan!
Okay!
Here we go.
Dear Heaven.
It's getting better.
Memory.
Two at a time.
Wait, no!
Hang in there, Heavenly Host!
Come on, Heavenly Host!
Oh, I feel it
Yay!
Here we go
Heavenly Master
Heavenly King
Amazing
There was a lot of heat, a lot of heat.
Oh, I made a mistake
Mello mello mello
Deliberating
Melo melo melo
I thought you said melonbos.
Berber berber berber
I want to give you a feeling I want to give you a feeling I want to give you a feeling I want to give you a feeling
I want to give it up
Yay! Melons!
Melons!
Why so many melons?
Our children.
You mean they're farmers?
Okay.
Kira!
Kira-san!
You're mixing them up!
Okay.
I thought we were all here at the same time.
That's a thousand entries.
First one was goo goo.
Not a millimeter back.
That's it.
Weren't they all at the same time?
Honesty is good.
First goo-goo goo.
First goo-goo goo goo.
Congratulations.
First time
OK
This is a little too much heat.
Don't you guys love it when they're OK?
Okay.
I'm gonna remember this so much.
Mr. Melon.
Why?
Who?
Takemoto?
Se-no.
I saw him.
Oh, good, there's a great current, but he's not sleeping, is he?
Boo boo
ren
Okeke kore!
I knew it!
Ai deka shoi ai deka shoi ai deka shoi ai deka shoi
Okekekakeko!
It has begun!
Okekekakeko
Cute!
Can eat with nose
You can eat it with your nose.
You can eat with your nose.
You said it twice. It doesn't make sense. It's rock, paper, scissors.
I'm really good at rock, paper, scissors.
Aiko, right? Aiko, right?
Jang-jang, Janken-Hui, Hi-Ya!
I lost.
Kira's face is awful!
Let's keep the heat.
Punch it!
I'm serious.
Oh, no!
That was unbelievably fast!
I had banana bangs.
I was talking about banana bangs.
Yui said it too.
He had a loud voice.
Yui's banana bangs!
Punch it!
Banana bangs!
Yuri was faster than me, but her voice was so loud
Hot!
It's no good if you lose because of the heat.
It's all about feelings, right?
I'll definitely give it a punch perm!
Aaah!
We're all doing it at the same time, right?
I don't know, I don't know.
This is the first time I've ever seen anyone get better.
Everybody gets better You just want to scream
Rasich, just shout what you think.
Before you see it, before you see it...
But, well, well... I've been thinking about a lot of things.
Sure, just for the camera.
You each scream, and if you get it right, you turn it over, and you get it right.
I'll take that. I'll close my eyes.
I'm gonna close my eyes and scream. I'm gonna close my eyes and scream.
I'm not thinking.
I'm sure it's her.
I'm sure she's in my mind.
I'm sure she's awake. Hey, guys.
I'll show you.
I'm pointing it at you now. Should I scream? This one.
Should I scream with my eyes closed?
Ready?
Oh!
What do I say?
What's the killer?
I'm a melon-boze.
I'm Spongebob.
Futon.
Empty eyes.
So, are we done?
I'll open my eyes.
Ready?
Oh!
I see it now!
I see it now! I see it now!
Oh, shit!
Oh, it's you!
Let's settle up without her.
That's a pretty good match, isn't it?
Five, six.
Let's see how fast you can stack them.
You know what I mean? Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, let's announce the number of sheets. Let's start with Takemoto-san, who seems to have the fewest.
What?
I just took a cold while speaking out loud, and you're standing next to me.
Hey! I thought.
Ten.
Here you go.
Nine.
Huh? Ah!
Ah, ah, 12.
Ah, ah, together, together.
Fourteen.
Oh, 14.
What?
This is the game!
Okay, I'll give it to you two one more time.
Keep your eyes closed.
What are you going to do? I'm in.
Okay, I'll do it.
I've made up my mind.
Okay?
Okay, then.
Can I scream?
Ready?
Melon-boos!
Beds!
Bedding and melon bozos.
Our choice.
Can I open my eyes?
Yes, you can.
Here he is.
Labbo!
Wow!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh!
That's seriously amazing!
Oh, my God!
That was amazing!
Why, why, why did you win?
Yes!
That's great!
I'm so happy.
How do you know?
How do you know, Melonball?
You're gonna make an elf out of me.
You know what I'm talking about.
He's so cute.
I'm so happy.
I guess.
Thank you very much.
If you want to play Najamonja, please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel.
Please do!
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
I'll be waiting for your comments.
I'll be waiting.
Which girl do you like?
Punch pants too
Punchy pants, too!